♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix it ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
You're the one who picked up Ibyang
the other day, right?
- How is she?
- She's been crying for several nights.
Can I see her?
[in English] Viktor Petrov,
ambassador of Zahran.
[Atoy, in English] Mr. Ambassador,
I am Alexei Sokolov.
[Mercado] If you have the chance
to get it now, do it.
But make sure you won't be compromised.
PREVIOUSLY
[Samir] Hey!
[in English] Sir, you are acting
very suspicious.
[in English] I will have to tell
the ambassador.
- [grunts]
- [Kurt gasps]
[Viktor, in Russian] What happened here?
[in English] This man…
This man harassed me!
[in English] Let's go.
[Kurt, in English] Emerson,
you should have seen it!
[in English] It was amazing!
We almost got caught!
- Go shampoo your hair. It'll come off.
- [in English] Okay.
Brother Atoy is so kind to us,
he needs to know the truth.
Do you really want
to repay his kindness with pain?
Karla, I'm begging you.
Don't tell him anything.
The question now is,
how do we extract the laptop?
If it's hard to enter the building
from the inside,
I'll do it from the outside.
- [Kurt] Oh.
- [music fades]
- [Karla] Thank you, brother.
- You're welcome!
[sneaky music playing]
[in English] Uncanny.
Brother, one order, takeout.
[in English] Karla,
did Atoy teach you that style?
[in English] Because that's exactly
how he prepares his pares.
No. This is just how I like it.
[in English] Weird.
[in English] You know, I've served
so many pares,
and, uh, besides Atoy,
I think you're the only one
I've ever seen who does it like that.
[in English] It's almost like, uh…
[in English] It's like, uh…
You're almost like brother and sister.
Right? [chuckles]
- [Kurt] Right?
- [Nestor] Uh-huh.
[Nestor] You said it,
Brother Kurt. You'd really think
Atoy is Karla's brother.
Mmm-hmm.
Look, they even have the same eyes.
- [Tukmol] You're right.
- Stop it already!
He's not my brother! You're so annoying!
Brother Kurt, wrap this up for me.
I'll just eat at home.
I need to buy something at the store.
I'll come back for it.
[music fades]
Karla is so moody. She's baffling.
Just like Atoy when he sulks.
[laughs]
- Psst, hey!
- No, it's true.
Pass me that-- This one.
[suave theme music playing]
[motorcycle revving]
[sewing machine whirring]
[scratches]
[snipping]
[sewing machine clacking]
- [gun cocks]
- [gunshots]
[gunshots]
[clacking]
[clicking]
[snipping]
[electronic blipping]
- [Ame] Ibyang!
- Hmm?
[Ame] Hey, Ibyang!
- [Cita sighs] Ibyang!
- Stop what you're doing.
We have a surprise for you!
What is it?
[Cita giggles]
[Cita sighs]
[Audrey] Hi, Ibyang.
[light music playing]
Hi.
I heard that… dumplings are your favorite.
So…
[paper rustling]
I brought some for you.
Oh? What do you say, child?
Thank you, but…
dumplings aren't my favorite anymore.
[melancholic music playing]
[Audrey] Really?
Since when?
Just now.
- You've earned a lot today.
- [indistinct]
Good thing the noisy ones are gone.
- [Kurt] Karla.
- Brother Kurt, my order.
Hey, uh, I'm really sorry
for what I said earlier,
about you and Atoy
being like brother and sister.
It's fine, Brother Kurt.
Wait.
Then why did you get mad?
Don't you want Atoy to be your brother?
Atoy is so kind to you.
[sighs]
If I didn't know you,
I'd really think you were siblings.
Honestly, Brother Atoy
is the best brother in the whole world.
Anyone would be lucky to be his sibling.
- But--
- Oh, so what's the problem?
It's okay, but… Not really.
It's complicated.
[pensive music playing]
I wish he were, but…
you shouldn't just wish for things.
There are consequences.
[in English] Wait, but…
What are you trying to say?
[in English] Because I'm-- I'm confused.
Actually, me too.
It's hard to explain.
Oh, Karla, don't think
about it anymore, okay?
Forget it, because
you're not really Atoy's sister.
The one to pity here is Ibyang.
Doesn't she live with Ame at your place?
[in English] Really?
[in English] I thought
they were with Atoy.
[Siony] Oh, not anymore!
I heard Atoy won't adopt Ibyang
because he already has his own child.
And he reconciled
with the mother of that child.
So Ibyang is left out.
- What's the name of that woman again?
- [Kurt] Oh.
[in English] You had all that gossip,
but you forgot the name?
Oh, I'm not a gossipmonger! [chuckles]
It's Ms. Audrey.
Ah, that's it.
I really feel sorry for Ibyang.
She really wanted
Brother Atoy to adopt her.
Mm-hmm.
[music fades]
I'll go ahead.
[somber music playing]
Ibyang…
I know you were hurt…
and upset with me.
[in English] And I'm sorry.
[melancholic music playing]
[sobs, in English] I'm sorry.
[Audrey, in English] I'm sorry.
I hope… [sighs]
you can forgive me.
Because I missed you.
I missed you, Ibyang.
I missed you too.
Really?
- [music fades]
- [soft chuckle]
[sentimental music playing]
[sobs]
[traffic noises]
- Audrey.
- Hi!
What-- What are you doing here?
Are you… Are you alone?
No, I'm with someone.
Um, Miss Cita
just stepped out for a while.
- Ah.
- [in English] Actually…
[pensive music playing]
I've been waiting for you.
Oh, uh…
How… How are you?
- Um…
- What…
- There's--
- I'm okay. You?
You look tired.
Are you okay?
Mm-hmm.
Um…
Have you eaten?
Maybe you want to have dinner?
Uh, shall we have dinner?
Uh, Audrey, well…
Excuse me, um…
I can't because…
I have work.
Sorry.
Atoy…
[music fades]
Do we have a problem?
[suspicious music playing]
[Dmitri, in English]
You seem like a good father.
[in English] But I don't want you
around my daughter,
much less marrying her
or building a family with her.
I don't want Audrey to think
I'm separating you.
[in English] But I know
what's best for her.
And it's not you.
[sighs]
[music fades]
That night I went to your house…
[pensive music playing]
When we had dinner.
Your father talked to me.
[in English] In short…
He wants me to stay away from you.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because you didn't need to know.
What for?
We're both adults. We know what we want.
And I know what I want.
Do you?
[somber music playing]
I know what I want too, Atoy.
Thank you.
At least now…
I feel more at ease
because I know what you want.
Next time, if we have a problem…
send me a text.
I understand you're busy.
[chuckles softly]
[sentimental music playing]
[Cita] Looks like… [chuckles softly]
you've made up.
[chuckles]
Did you tell her?
He already told me
what he and Dad talked about.
[music fades]
Godmother, where's Karla?
I've been calling her.
She's not answering.
Even by text.
I have a job I want to give her.
[Cita] Hmm…
Uh, maybe she's busy.
[Atoy] Busy?
[pensive music playing]
What job are you giving Karla?
Karla usually drives me when I have a gig.
Usually, when I call her,
she answers quickly.
But now, it's like…
Maybe she really is busy.
That's why I'm worried
who I'll call instead.
- [music fades]
- [sighs]
Hmm? I'm game.
When is it? I can do it now.
Eh, Emerson, just a warning, okay.
What we're about to do is dangerous.
The national security
of our country depends on this.
You can't fail. Do you understand?
[Atoy] Failure is not allowed.
I might not come back.
We'll defend the country. I'll be a hero.
A hero, but in the grave.
That won't happen! Not with you!
[in English] I got your back, bro!
We can do this. Let's claim it!
Just make sure.
Because I don't want to leave
my loved ones behind.
Prepare yourself.
[rock music playing]
[muffled chattering in the distance]
Ibyang!
Look at this student, very cute.
Here. Uh, your lunch.
Uh, Tatoy prepared this for you.
[somber music playing]
Uh… Here, take this.
Uh… He said…
you should do well in school, and…
don't get into fights, okay?
Don't give your teachers a headache.
[in English] Okay?
Go ahead.
Eat this. He said it's delicious.
[chuckles]
There you go.
He really doesn't want to see me, huh?
Because he wasn't the one waiting for me.
[somber music playing]
Uh, uh-- No.
It's because he has a big mission,
so it's difficult.
And he said
you should pray for him
to San Antonio de Padua, so
he can find and get what he needs
and he can come home safely to us.
Emerson, we'll go ahead, okay.
- The child might be late.
- Yes, okay.
- Oh, all right.
- Oh, go ahead. All right.
[in English] Bye-bye!
[bright music playing]
Please give this to him.
Tell him to read it
before he does his mission.
If not, I'll be even angrier.
I walked so far,
I thought you were following me.
Come on. You'll be late.
Okay. Sure, I'll deliver it.
Take care, okay?
Oh, come on. I'll do it. Come on.
You're late. I walked so far already.
- [music fades]
- [sewing machine whirring]
[soft rock music playing]
Where did you lose your ID badge, Ben?
[Ben] If I knew,
I would've found it already.
How long does it take to replace it?
[security guard] I'll just notify
my replacement at the service entrance.
[Ben] Just make sure
the spelling is correct.
Ben Laput. It's letter U, not letter O.
[music fades]
[Emerson] Atoy!
Oh?
Is it good? Mm.
[whimsical music playing]
What's with the look?
Of course.
I want to show you that…
I'm better than Brother Kurt.
Especially when it comes to disguises,
so you'll always bring me
on your missions.
Right? Mm.
- I look like--
- You're even wearing a leather jacket
and gloves. What for--
Well, of course, race car driver style.
Race car driver? You look like a goon.
- Huh?
- Take it off!
That's not needed. Too-- Too over the top.
We'll get noticed.
Take it off?
It should be simple.
I even worked hard to look like this.
You. Fine. Oh.
Okay.
By the way, here.
[music fades]
Ibyang asked me to give this.
[Emerson] Mm-hmm.
This look is different, huh.
Right?
Here, even the gloves.
[bright music playing]
Ibyang said we should be careful,
because if something bad happens to me,
she won't talk to me for 20 million years.
[Emerson giggles]
So, we need to be careful.
Oh, well… To be sure,
I'll block the person
whose face you copied.
Yes, I need Ben to be gone
for about three hours,
so I can do what I need to do.
Three?!
Three hours?!
What will I do for three hours there?
What, sew him a barong?
What, give him a manicure and pedicure
just to keep him there?
- Three hours is long, Atoy.
- You can do it.
Just listen carefully.
Ben will arrive before two o'clock.
Okay? Then, when I enter,
I'll probably need at least
two hours to get the device.
So, listen carefully.
Our planned coordination,
you can't mess up.
- Okay, fine.
- [in English] Copy?
[in English] Copy. Oh, from the top.
Go ahead. Come again?
No. Go ahead, tell me. I'll remember it.
- Three hours.
- Three hours. Okay?
Just three hours. Find a way.
Whatever it takes. Block him.
[inaudible]
[birds chirping]
Where's the party, Dad?
[in English] I was invited
by a good friend of mine.
[in English] He's kind of a big deal.
Unless you're busy or…
you have plans with Atoy.
Not really.
[in English] Um, he'll be preoccupied
for the next few days.
[sighs] Child…
Are you really sure about Atoy?
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] What are you
trying to say, Dad?
[in English] All I'm saying is…
You know that Atoy's work
as a tracker is dangerous.
You and your daughter
might get caught up in it.
Dad, be honest with me.
You don't want Atoy for me, do you?
[in English] I'm just worried about you
and my grandchild.
Atoy is a good man.
[in English] Everyone has a secret, child.
Especially someone like Atoy.
[in English] I just want you
to be careful.
[in English] Always.
[in English] Okay?
[music fades]
[rousing music playing]
[Atoy] I'll position myself
near the entrance, right side.
Okay?
Watch for Ben on the left.
That's where he'll come from.
This must be it. This is it.
[Atoy] When you see Ben, act drunk
and like you've known him for a long time.
That's the acting.
Ben, my friend!
[Atoy] You have to be persistent!
Ben, my friend! Ben, my friend!
Hey! How are you?
[chuckles] What's the news, my friend?
Oh?
How are you?
Do we know each other?
Hey, yes!
We even bumped
into each other at the market recently!
- So, what's up?
- Huh? When was that?
[Atoy] Once you've got him, I'll go in.
That's it.
[soft rock music playing]
- At the market, and--
- Huh? When?
[music swells]
[music fades]
- [tense music playing]
- [sighs]
Still him?
[in English] What did you say?
[in English] You can't get over
that businessman
because of what he did to your face, huh?
[suspicious music playing]
[clamoring]
[Kurt gasps]
- [in English] Alexei! What are you doing
- [in English] Brother!
to my brother, huh?!
[in English] Your brother
is the one who hit me first!
[in English] Yes.
[in English] Everyone is in position.
[in English] The ambassador's guests
for the party will be here soon.
[in English] Look at him.
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] Does it look like
he's looking for the bathroom?
Hmm?
[in English] It looks like
he wants to go into the office.
[in English] I want you
to check his profile.
[in English] His name is Alexei Sokolov.
[in English] Okay, sir.
[tense music playing]
[woman] Samir got hit
right on the forehead.
- Oh?
- [woman] Yes.
- He even looked cross-eyed, that fool.
- [chuckles]
He is arrogant.
Too bad I didn't see his face.
- [chuckles]
- Like this?
[chuckles]
But Samir said he'll look
for the businessman he fought with.
What do you think he plans to do?
[woman] Hmm, maybe he wants
to even the score.
[laughs]
Maybe. Thank you, sir.
[woman] Thank you!
[suspicious music playing]
Bro, is this where
you get the replacement ID?
What's your name?
Ben Laput.
Uh, Laput. Letter U, not letter O.
There's a Ben Laput here,
claiming an ID badge.
[radio static]
[security guard] The one
with the scar on his face?
That's our window cleaner.
[radio static]
[music fades]
[tense music playing]
Is that still necessary, boss?
We've got a lot of work to do.
We're in a hurry.
[security guard] Is this your bag?
Yes.
[Atoy clears throat]
[music swells]
[device beeping]
What are you carrying here?
[intense music playing]
- [electronic blipping]
- [tense music playing]
UP NEXT
I-I just wanted to let you know
I'm here now at the embassy of Zahran.
[Atoy] What?! What are you doing
here at the embassy?
How long will you keep avoiding Atoy?
I can't face Brother Atoy
because I feel guilty.
But you didn't do anything wrong.
I'm not like you guys who have thick skin.
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
‪♪ ‪Fix it‪ ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias